<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>people on Yifei Xu</title><link>yfxu.net/tags/people/</link><description>Recent content in people on Yifei Xu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-ca</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 14:34:01 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="yfxu.net/tags/people/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DSCF7242</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/cafe-snc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 14:34:01 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/cafe-snc/</guid><description>Not a sponsored post
This guy made some extremely banger curry.</description></item><item><title>DSCF5755</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/sakurain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 20:07:11 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/sakurain/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Delivery</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/delivery/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 13:20:57 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/delivery/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DSCF5431</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/the-director/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 13:15:54 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/the-director/</guid><description>This photo was taken from up on top of a little bridge connecting two buildings in the Tsukiji Outer Market. I don&amp;rsquo;t remember how intentional this photo was, but I think the traffic director looks super cool in this composition.
I noticed that there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of people working as these types of traffic control officers in Japan. They work late into the nights guarding building garage entrances too. It must get kinda cold doing that type of job late at night.</description></item><item><title>Hot Dog Stand</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/hot-dog-stand/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 06:46:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/hot-dog-stand/</guid><description>I was trying to get one of those really cool urban neon-Tokyo vibes shots of a man chilling at a food stall underneath neon lights. I think my composition kinda sucked though because I felt quite self-conscious about photographing strangers, which may or may not be a good thing. I&amp;rsquo;d like to make my photos have a more human and present feeling to them though.</description></item><item><title>Akihabara Overblown</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/akihabara-overblown/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 12:03:59 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/akihabara-overblown/</guid><description>I process most of my images through Filmulator. While playing around with the settings, I found a way to really make the image look a bit deep fried and oversaturated, blasted with colours that you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t actually see in real life. This is one of my photographs which met such a demise. I think it&amp;rsquo;s fitting though, given how colorful Akihabara actually still is, despite not necessarily being &amp;ldquo;deep fried&amp;rdquo; irl.</description></item><item><title>DSCF4447</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/eerie-path/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 15:10:25 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/eerie-path/</guid><description>This was another shot I took during my ascent of Takaosan with some co-op friends in Japan. The thick fog is really cool for making strange, eerie photos.</description></item><item><title>Fleeting Respite</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/fleeting-respite/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 21:02:02 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/fleeting-respite/</guid><description>Shibuya Yokochou is a magical and noisy street filled with small restaurants along one side of the entire street. It&amp;rsquo;s got that super down-to-earth cheap wooden tables and plastic chairs vibe all about, where people can yap about their lives and stuff while chowing down chicken skewers and beer. The entire street glows with a comfy amber aura throughout the evening while customers come and go.
The first time I came here, I vowed to never eat at any of the restaurants until my girlfriend would eventually come visit in Japan 7 months later.</description></item></channel></rss>