<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>indoor_scene on Yifei Xu</title><link>/tags/indoor_scene/</link><description>Recent content in indoor_scene on Yifei Xu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-ca</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 23:54:37 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/indoor_scene/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Horrible</title><link>/gallery/horrible/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 23:54:37 -0500</pubDate><guid>/gallery/horrible/</guid><description>These vibes are just straight horrible. Backrooms-lookin ass SCP K-Class scenario type beat.</description></item><item><title>DSCF1111</title><link>/gallery/fire-sign/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 23:44:35 -0500</pubDate><guid>/gallery/fire-sign/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Hypnosis</title><link>/gallery/hypnosis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 23:42:35 -0500</pubDate><guid>/gallery/hypnosis/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DSCF9948</title><link>/gallery/kitchen-sink/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 15:09:46 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/kitchen-sink/</guid><description>In case you&amp;rsquo;re wondering what&amp;rsquo;s attached to the faucet, those are the pipes connected to a detachable dishwasher unit!
The house didn&amp;rsquo;t come with a dishwasher when it was built, so I guess some previous tenants bought a separate one. It was kind of annoying using it though, because you&amp;rsquo;re just not able to have a good user experience using the sink while it&amp;rsquo;s connected to the dishwasher.
There&amp;rsquo;s a little red button on the valve connected to the faucet that when pressed, will let the sink water flow out through the bottom.</description></item><item><title>DSCF9889</title><link>/gallery/bookstore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 16:33:05 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/bookstore/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Jaundice</title><link>/gallery/jaundice/</link><pubDate>Fri, 21 Jul 2023 07:13:52 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/jaundice/</guid><description>This wall looks DISGUSTING! In a good way (I think?) I took this photo in the men&amp;rsquo;s room of a rather dilapidated Toys R&amp;rsquo; Us. I didn&amp;rsquo;t capture any photos of the bathroom stalls, but they were painted this really nasty rotting seafoam green that just didn&amp;rsquo;t compliment anything in the room at all. And the floor tiles also had this gross yellowing on them that brought me back into a VHS-era local community centre.</description></item><item><title>DSCF8801</title><link>/gallery/corner-store/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 12:18:08 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/corner-store/</guid><description>For 2 months during the summer this photo was taken, I worked full-time at a grocery store! It was a goal of mine for quite a while to experience working a job that isn&amp;rsquo;t just software engineering, where I sit in the same desk in front of the same computer screen and talk to the same people every day1, and so when I finally had an off-term from school, I was super stoked to try new things.</description></item><item><title>DSCF8767</title><link>/gallery/green-cafe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:37:40 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/green-cafe/</guid><description>I went on some like six hour walk in Vancouver downtown on the day I took this photo. There&amp;rsquo;s such a good feeling in just being able to pick any random location to go, and then actually go there. As dumb as it sounds, I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m in control of the world. Or I guess just my world.</description></item><item><title>Step Right Up</title><link>/gallery/step-right-up/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 May 2023 21:07:12 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/step-right-up/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DSCF7242</title><link>/gallery/cafe-snc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 14:34:01 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/cafe-snc/</guid><description>Not a sponsored post
This guy made some extremely banger curry.</description></item><item><title>Telephone</title><link>/gallery/telephone/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 12:50:01 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/telephone/</guid><description>In Kyoto, we stumbled across this HUGE temple smack dab in the middle of the city. It wasn&amp;rsquo;t in our plans to visit it but the building was just so unbelievably wide and tall; we had to check it out. Unfortunately I wasn&amp;rsquo;t able to capture any photos of the inside as photography was prohibited.
Right next to the temple is a little visitor&amp;rsquo;s centre, and that building somehow was just built with so many different rooms and spaces.</description></item><item><title>Train Cabin</title><link>/gallery/train-cabin/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 13:07:38 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/train-cabin/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Busy Dinner</title><link>/gallery/busy-dinner/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 21:39:05 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/busy-dinner/</guid><description>I love the chaotic energy of Izakayas.</description></item><item><title>20210922_224502</title><link>/gallery/audio-visual-room/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 22:45:01 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/audio-visual-room/</guid><description>Isn&amp;rsquo;t this wall just so yellow??
I found this wall while roaming around the Life Building on UBC campus with Jasmine during some late night study trip. Or at least I think we were studying. Surely I was studying like a good student right? :D</description></item><item><title>20201030_110204</title><link>/gallery/offline/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 11:02:04 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/offline/</guid><description>The lighting in my bedroom was simply too impeccable at the time to pass up on quick photo. I love the moodiness in this photo, combined with the black electric fan that almost looks like it&amp;rsquo;s feeling sad, head tilted downwards, staring at the floor, standing out of the sunlight.</description></item></channel></rss>