<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>yfxu</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on yfxu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>On Cybersecurity and Parenting</title><link>/posts/on-cybersecurity-and-parenting/</link><pubDate>Tue, 23 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/on-cybersecurity-and-parenting/</guid><description>A few weeks ago, I had the opportunity to listen in on an online cybersecurity presentation delivered live by Paul Davis. He&amp;rsquo;s both a father and an experienced IT professional who now works as an educator and advocator for online safety, frequently appearing as a guest speaker at schools and on TV.
The virtual speech that I attended was directed towards parents of middle school students, offering insight on what parents should be doing for their kids in our current digital age, and what they can do themselves to enhance their own digital privacy.</description></item><item><title>The Illusion of Disagreement</title><link>/posts/the-illusion-of-disagreement/</link><pubDate>Sun, 21 Nov 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/the-illusion-of-disagreement/</guid><description>Earlier today, Jasmine and I were playing a game called &amp;ldquo;Wavelength.&amp;rdquo; It&amp;rsquo;s a pretty simple game where two or more players take turns guessing how much or how little some clue represents a certain quality. Ok maybe that&amp;rsquo;s a bit confusing. Here&amp;rsquo;s an example:
Player 1 is given two different words: &amp;ldquo;disgusting&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;delicious&amp;rdquo;. These two words are placed on a 10-point scale with 1 being disgusting, and 10 being delicious.</description></item><item><title>Things I Wish My Teachers Did Differently</title><link>/posts/things-i-wish-my-teachers-did-differently/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Oct 2021 19:52:29 -0600</pubDate><guid>/posts/things-i-wish-my-teachers-did-differently/</guid><description>This post serves as a letter to myself in the future if I ever decide to become a better teacher. ALSO I recognize that I am one individual student with my own learning needs. People have different things they each need to excel!
Teaching the context I wish that teachers placed more emphasis on the context surrounding any arbitrary topics. As a student, it&amp;rsquo;s hard to engage myself with the course content when I don&amp;rsquo;t even know why we&amp;rsquo;re learning it.</description></item><item><title>Conveying Emotion Through Text</title><link>/posts/conveying-emotion-through-text/</link><pubDate>Sat, 13 Mar 2021 23:32:51 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/conveying-emotion-through-text/</guid><description>Disclaimer: Please don&amp;rsquo;t take this post too seriously
Do YOU want to spice up your online messaging style??? Well you&amp;rsquo;ve come to the right place! Here are some tips to make people think you&amp;rsquo;re friggin out of your mind:
RAnDom CapiTALiZatIon Useful when mocking something or just wanting to sound very over-the-top for any reason. Capitalization can also indicate where you&amp;rsquo;d normally change your tone/pitch to emphasize things.
A: Holy shit man did you see Cookiezi&amp;rsquo;s choke on Blue Zenith?</description></item><item><title>Decomplexifying the Internet</title><link>/posts/decomplexifying-the-internet/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Feb 2021 01:02:58 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/decomplexifying-the-internet/</guid><description>How to make the internet less fucky&amp;mdash;and whether or not that&amp;rsquo;s actually a good thing
A habit I&amp;rsquo;ve gotten into recently is sending the original URLs of images instead of copy + pasting them to friends. The rationale behind this is to avoid unnecessary redundancy. For every image that gets copy + pasted onto some messaging platform, the user is effectively uploading a new file to the server (and probably for free).</description></item><item><title>Four Years of osu! Mapping</title><link>/posts/four-years-of-osu-mapping/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 11:51:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/four-years-of-osu-mapping/</guid><description>The Start 2017-01-28 ‣ An - 花柳采 (Karyuusai) About 4 years ago, I published Karyuusai as my first serious attempt at making an osu! beatmap—meaning it was a pretty bad map. It had no structure, poor rhythm choices, and fairly garbage-tier aesthetics. But I kept mapping anyway, and I like to think that I got a little better making beatmaps since. Since I&amp;rsquo;ve spent so much time on this game, I figured I&amp;rsquo;d document my journey and some of the things I learned over these past 4 years as a tribute of sorts to that beatmap.</description></item><item><title>An Adventure in Building osulist</title><link>/posts/an-adventure-in-building-osulist/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 14:23:50 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/an-adventure-in-building-osulist/</guid><description>https://osulist.tk/
One of my favorite computer games is osu! (exclamation mark included) It&amp;rsquo;s a free rhythm game where the player&amp;rsquo;s goal is to click a bunch of circles that appear on the screen to the beat of a song. Songs are referred to as &amp;ldquo;beatmaps,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;maps&amp;rdquo; for short.
Over time, something I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed is that there isn&amp;rsquo;t a really great way to share multiple beatmaps with your friends. Say you&amp;rsquo;ve found a few beatmaps that you really like, and you want your friend to try playing them.</description></item><item><title>Getting Back Into Blogging</title><link>/posts/getting-back-into-blogging/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 20:48:20 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/getting-back-into-blogging/</guid><description>Back in early 2016, I created a Tumblr account because God knows why. Aha, actually it&amp;rsquo;s because I sorta wanted to exercise my writing skills somewhere outside of school, and blogging seemed like a cool way to achieve that. Part of me actually enjoyed writing because it was a nice way to sort out some thoughts in my head, and overall, it was just a peaceful experience.
At the time, I thought my posts were pretty cool.</description></item><item><title>Thoughts on Design</title><link>/posts/thoughts-on-design/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 20:48:20 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/thoughts-on-design/</guid><description>Many of my friends are well-invested into various forms of arts, either as hobbyists or professionals. So I hear a lot about the zeitgeist™ of whatever art communities are relevant at the time. As a result, I also start thinking more about art and its value (but usually it&amp;rsquo;s nothing more significant than &amp;ldquo;wohaoh this art looks very cool&amp;rdquo;).
Someone I know, being a part-time UI designer, spread their interest in graphic design over to me.</description></item></channel></rss>