<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>vehicles on Yifei Xu</title><link>/tags/vehicles/</link><description>Recent content in vehicles on Yifei Xu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-ca</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 18:09:03 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/vehicles/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Stearns Wharf</title><link>/gallery/stearns-wharf/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 18:09:03 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/stearns-wharf/</guid><description>I never grew up around the ocean, but sometimes I feel like I was a fisherman in a past life. I&amp;rsquo;ve discovered that one of the most blissful feelings to ever experience is the sensation of the ocean breeze flowing past your face as you smell the salty air and listen to the waves gently crash over and over again. I think I could sit on this pier and just look out into the distance for a while without having any thoughts cross my mind.</description></item><item><title>DSCF6123</title><link>/gallery/mt-fuji-from-owakudani/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 16:37:24 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/mt-fuji-from-owakudani/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Delivery</title><link>/gallery/delivery/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 13:20:57 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/delivery/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Drugstore</title><link>/gallery/drugstore/</link><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2022 10:40:35 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/drugstore/</guid><description/></item><item><title>It's Getting Dark</title><link>/gallery/its-getting-dark/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 17:00:54 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/its-getting-dark/</guid><description>Story time! Japan celebrates a statutory holiday called &amp;ldquo;Sports Day&amp;rdquo; every year. It&amp;rsquo;s a day dedicated to the pursuit of health and longevity through physical activities and general healthy lifestyle choices.
To celebrate this day, I joined a few of my fellow co-op student friends on a day trip to hike Mount Takao, or &amp;ldquo;Takaosan,&amp;rdquo; as the Japanese name would be romanized. Mount Takao is relatively accessible from central Tokyo, with a single train line travelling from Shinjuku Station all the way to the foot of Mount Takao.</description></item><item><title>20210828_193529</title><link>/gallery/red-building/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 19:35:28 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/red-building/</guid><description>I took this photo while waiting in line for some apparently CRAZY GOOD ramen at Ramen Danbo! The line did not lie, the ramen was worth lining up for. I got some spicy ramen that my stomach didn&amp;rsquo;t end up quite agreeing with, but it was still an enjoyable experience! I think?</description></item></channel></rss>