<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>gallery on Yifei Xu</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/</link><description>Recent content in gallery on Yifei Xu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-ca</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 15:09:46 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="yfxu.net/gallery/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DSCF9948</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/kitchen-sink/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 15:09:46 -0700</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/kitchen-sink/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Stearns Wharf</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/stearns-wharf/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 18:09:03 -0700</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/stearns-wharf/</guid><description>I never grew up around the ocean, but sometimes I feel like I was a fisherman in a past life. I&amp;rsquo;ve discovered that one of the most blissful feelings to ever experience is the sensation of the ocean breeze flowing past your face as you smell the salty air and listen to the waves gently crash over and over again. I think I could sit on this pier and just look out into the distance for a while without having any thoughts cross my mind.</description></item><item><title>DSCF9400</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/santa-barbara-palm-trees/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 17:32:56 -0700</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/santa-barbara-palm-trees/</guid><description>Honestly this is kinda just a filler photo to put in the gallery to make myself seem more well-travelled ! aHA !
This photo was taken on a short trip with my girlfriend when we visited her Dad in Los Angeles. We spent 2 days in Santa Barbara, and it was the first time in many years that I&amp;rsquo;d been to a token California beach.
It was hot and humid, and neither my girlfriend nor I were able to think with more than six combined brain cells because we were both physically and mentally melting in real life!</description></item><item><title>DSCF8801</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/corner-store/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 15:18:08 -0700</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/corner-store/</guid><description>For 2 months during the summer this photo was taken, I worked full-time at a grocery store! It was a goal of mine for quite a while to experience working a job that isn&amp;rsquo;t just software engineering, where I sit in the same desk in front of the same computer screen and talk to the same people every day1, and so when I finally had an off-term from school, I was super stoked to try new things.</description></item><item><title>DSCF7817</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/cosmo-clock/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Jun 2023 18:41:55 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/cosmo-clock/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DSCF7242</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/cafe-snc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 14:34:01 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/cafe-snc/</guid><description>Not a sponsored post
This guy made some extremely banger curry.</description></item><item><title>DSCF6961</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/red-umbrella/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 15:41:21 -0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/red-umbrella/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DSCF6123</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/mt-fuji-from-owakudani/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 16:37:24 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/mt-fuji-from-owakudani/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DSCF5839</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/naka-meguro-overblown/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 12:23:23 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/naka-meguro-overblown/</guid><description>This place gets reaaaaaal busy during Hanami, and understandably so. I came here on multiple different occasions just to take pictures of the cherry blossoms because yeah I&amp;rsquo;m basic like that.
But don&amp;rsquo;t worry, I made sure to get lots of random things in this picture to make it unique, and I also tuned up the saturation way past what they actually look like in real life. Rest assured, Naka-Meguro is still a very pretty place in person even if your eyeballs don&amp;rsquo;t have the latest saturation-boosting mods installed.</description></item><item><title>DSCF5755</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/sakurain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 20:07:11 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/sakurain/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DSCF5603</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/chinatown/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 20:40:05 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/chinatown/</guid><description>Usually you&amp;rsquo;re supposed to go back home with your family to celebrate Chinese New Year, much like Thanksgiving or Christmas. But I, being all alone in Tokyo, was unable to visit home, so I decided to just visit Yokohama Chinatown to see what was going on over there. Maybe I just got there too late or something, but there actually weren&amp;rsquo;t too many people. Some gift shops and restaurants were still open and all, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t seem all that lively.</description></item><item><title>Delivery</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/delivery/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 13:20:57 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/delivery/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DSCF5431</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/the-director/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 13:15:54 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/the-director/</guid><description>This photo was taken from up on top of a little bridge connecting two buildings in the Tsukiji Outer Market. I don&amp;rsquo;t remember how intentional this photo was, but I think the traffic director looks super cool in this composition.
I noticed that there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of people working as these types of traffic control officers in Japan. They work late into the nights guarding building garage entrances too. It must get kinda cold doing that type of job late at night.</description></item><item><title>Hot Dog Stand</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/hot-dog-stand/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 06:46:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/hot-dog-stand/</guid><description>I was trying to get one of those really cool urban neon-Tokyo vibes shots of a man chilling at a food stall underneath neon lights. I think my composition kinda sucked though because I felt quite self-conscious about photographing strangers, which may or may not be a good thing. I&amp;rsquo;d like to make my photos have a more human and present feeling to them though.</description></item><item><title>DSCF5198</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/listless-dream/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 13:05:38 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/listless-dream/</guid><description>This photo was taken while I was riding the Tobu-Nikko line, somewhere in the middle of Saitama City. It&amp;rsquo;s got such a dreamy, liminal quality it has from the blurred subjects and overexposed whites with a little bit of the cold blue sky still present. It&amp;rsquo;s one of the few photos I&amp;rsquo;ve taken that really evokes emotion in me whenever I see it. What emotion that is, I really do not know how to describe.</description></item><item><title>Akihabara Overblown</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/akihabara-overblown/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 12:03:59 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/akihabara-overblown/</guid><description>I process most of my images through Filmulator. While playing around with the settings, I found a way to really make the image look a bit deep fried and oversaturated, blasted with colours that you wouldn&amp;rsquo;t actually see in real life. This is one of my photographs which met such a demise. I think it&amp;rsquo;s fitting though, given how colorful Akihabara actually still is, despite not necessarily being &amp;ldquo;deep fried&amp;rdquo; irl.</description></item><item><title>DSCF4626</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/tight-squeeze/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Oct 2022 23:19:49 +0000</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/tight-squeeze/</guid><description>Just a cool a little alley I stumbled across. There&amp;rsquo;s lots of these in Japan :D</description></item><item><title>It's Getting Dark</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/its-getting-dark/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 17:00:54 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/its-getting-dark/</guid><description>Story time! Japan celebrates a statutory holiday called &amp;ldquo;Sports Day&amp;rdquo; every year. It&amp;rsquo;s a day dedicated to the pursuit of health and longevity through physical activities and general healthy lifestyle choices.
To celebrate this day, I joined a few of my fellow co-op student friends on a day trip to hike Mount Takao, or &amp;ldquo;Takaosan,&amp;rdquo; as the Japanese name would be romanized. Mount Takao is relatively accessible from central Tokyo, with a single train line travelling from Shinjuku Station all the way to the foot of Mount Takao.</description></item><item><title>DSCF4450</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/mysterious-stairs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 15:14:04 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/mysterious-stairs/</guid><description>Here&amp;rsquo;s some cool mysterious stairs we saw from when I hiked Mount Takao with some friends. There were an awful lot of stairs on this mountain hike. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it made things easier or worse to be honest.</description></item><item><title>DSCF4447</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/eerie-path/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 15:10:25 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/eerie-path/</guid><description>This was another shot I took during my ascent of Takaosan with some co-op friends in Japan. The thick fog is really cool for making strange, eerie photos.</description></item><item><title>Fleeting Respite</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/fleeting-respite/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 21:02:02 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/fleeting-respite/</guid><description>Shibuya Yokochou is a magical and noisy street filled with small restaurants along one side of the entire street. It&amp;rsquo;s got that super down-to-earth cheap wooden tables and plastic chairs vibe all about, where people can yap about their lives and stuff while chowing down chicken skewers and beer. The entire street glows with a comfy amber aura throughout the evening while customers come and go.
The first time I came here, I vowed to never eat at any of the restaurants until my girlfriend would eventually come visit in Japan 7 months later.</description></item><item><title>NOW PLAYING</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/now-playing/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Sep 2022 12:58:10 +0600</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/now-playing/</guid><description>There&amp;rsquo;s this really cool retro-style pink-coloured snack bar inside the theatre with neon signs and cool popcorn machines and one of those signs with blocky letters that you attach to pegholes and anyways it was just a very nice vibe.
I asked the guy working there if it was alright to take a photo of him working there because I thought of this whole composition in my mind where it&amp;rsquo;s some dude doing his local small cinema tasks next to the popcorn machine and the candy jars and anyways he said &amp;ldquo;No.</description></item><item><title>GULF OF GEORGIA CANNERY</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/gulf-of-georgia-cannery/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 18:22:51 -0700</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/gulf-of-georgia-cannery/</guid><description>Just a shot of a building I saw at the Steveston Fisherman&amp;rsquo;s Wharf. I liked the lens flare that I accidentally got in the photo. It gives the photo a bit of a nostalgic feeling.</description></item><item><title>20220417_162453</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/large-green-bridge/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 16:24:53 -0800</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/large-green-bridge/</guid><description>The bridge was very green and the sky was very blue so I was like &amp;ldquo;mmm yes cool shot&amp;rdquo; and then I took the photo.</description></item><item><title>20210922_224502</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/audio-visual-room/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 22:45:01 -0700</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/audio-visual-room/</guid><description>Isn&amp;rsquo;t this wall just so yellow??
I found this wall while roaming around the Life Building on UBC campus with Jasmine during some late night study trip. Or at least I think we were studying. Surely I was studying like a good student right? :D</description></item><item><title>20210828_193529</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/red-building/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 19:35:28 -0700</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/red-building/</guid><description>I took this photo while waiting in line for some apparently CRAZY GOOD ramen at Ramen Danbo! The line did not lie, the ramen was worth lining up for. I got some spicy ramen that my stomach didn&amp;rsquo;t end up quite agreeing with, but it was still an enjoyable experience! I think?</description></item><item><title>Cool Rock I Found</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/cool-rock-i-found/</link><pubDate>Thu, 13 May 2021 15:50:56 -0600</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/cool-rock-i-found/</guid><description>I found this rock existing in its natural state. Look how happy it is! It&amp;rsquo;s even got a fresh cut, so rad&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Silver Dragon</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/silver-dragon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2021 21:33:28 -0600</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/silver-dragon/</guid><description>Curious how it&amp;rsquo;s called the SILVER DRAGON yet the sign looks awfully golden&amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>Suburban Cabana</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/suburban-cabana/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 01:18:41 -0600</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/suburban-cabana/</guid><description>I was just going for some generic infrastructure shots in this little community courtyard/garden area in Calgary, and I got this shot that looked a lot more like a travel advertisement for some nice California beaches or something. Pretty neat considering this was in Calgary!</description></item><item><title>20201030_110204</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/offline/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 11:02:04 -0700</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/offline/</guid><description>The lighting in my bedroom was simply too impeccable at the time to pass up on quick photo. I love the moodiness in this photo, combined with the black electric fan that almost looks like it&amp;rsquo;s feeling sad, head tilted downwards, staring at the floor, standing out of the sunlight.</description></item></channel></rss>