<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>food_and_drink on Yifei Xu</title><link>/tags/food_and_drink/</link><description>Recent content in food_and_drink on Yifei Xu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-ca</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 12:18:08 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/food_and_drink/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DSCF8801</title><link>/gallery/corner-store/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 12:18:08 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/corner-store/</guid><description>For 2 months during the summer this photo was taken, I worked full-time at a grocery store! It was a goal of mine for quite a while to experience working a job that isn&amp;rsquo;t just software engineering, where I sit in the same desk in front of the same computer screen and talk to the same people every day1, and so when I finally had an off-term from school, I was super stoked to try new things.</description></item><item><title>DSCF8767</title><link>/gallery/green-cafe/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 11:37:40 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/green-cafe/</guid><description>I went on some like six hour walk in Vancouver downtown on the day I took this photo. There&amp;rsquo;s such a good feeling in just being able to pick any random location to go, and then actually go there. As dumb as it sounds, I feel like I&amp;rsquo;m in control of the world. Or I guess just my world.</description></item><item><title>DSCF7242</title><link>/gallery/cafe-snc/</link><pubDate>Fri, 12 May 2023 14:34:01 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/cafe-snc/</guid><description>Not a sponsored post
This guy made some extremely banger curry.</description></item><item><title>Busy Dinner</title><link>/gallery/busy-dinner/</link><pubDate>Sun, 06 Nov 2022 21:39:05 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/busy-dinner/</guid><description>I love the chaotic energy of Izakayas.</description></item><item><title>Fleeting Respite</title><link>/gallery/fleeting-respite/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 21:02:02 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/fleeting-respite/</guid><description>Shibuya Yokochou is a magical and noisy street filled with small restaurants along one side of the entire street. It&amp;rsquo;s got that super down-to-earth cheap wooden tables and plastic chairs vibe all about, where people can yap about their lives and stuff while chowing down chicken skewers and beer. The entire street glows with a comfy amber aura throughout the evening while customers come and go.
The first time I came here, I vowed to never eat at any of the restaurants until my girlfriend would eventually come visit in Japan 7 months later.</description></item></channel></rss>