<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>lights on Yifei Xu</title><link>/tags/lights/</link><description>Recent content in lights on Yifei Xu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-ca</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 21:02:25 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/lights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Sparks</title><link>/gallery/sparks/</link><pubDate>Wed, 20 Dec 2023 21:02:25 -0800</pubDate><guid>/gallery/sparks/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Semi Truck at 2:45 AM</title><link>/gallery/semi-at-2am/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 02:45:27 -0800</pubDate><guid>/gallery/semi-at-2am/</guid><description>This photo actually has a somewhat funny story behind it :D
Sometime during 2am, my friend and roommate Mia told us that it looked friggin crazy outside. I guess she saw some fog outside her bedroom window? In any case, she ran out with her camera, and so obviously I had to run out with my own camera as well.
The atmosphere was chilly and misty. The droplets of mist lingering in the air diffused the amber glow from the streetlights around us.</description></item><item><title>DSCF9948</title><link>/gallery/kitchen-sink/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 15:09:46 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/kitchen-sink/</guid><description>In case you&amp;rsquo;re wondering what&amp;rsquo;s attached to the faucet, those are the pipes connected to a detachable dishwasher unit!
The house didn&amp;rsquo;t come with a dishwasher when it was built, so I guess some previous tenants bought a separate one. It was kind of annoying using it though, because you&amp;rsquo;re just not able to have a good user experience using the sink while it&amp;rsquo;s connected to the dishwasher.
There&amp;rsquo;s a little red button on the valve connected to the faucet that when pressed, will let the sink water flow out through the bottom.</description></item><item><title>DSCF9889</title><link>/gallery/bookstore/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Oct 2023 16:33:05 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/bookstore/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Ruby</title><link>/gallery/ruby/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Jul 2023 13:46:37 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/ruby/</guid><description>Long exposure photography is pretty brainlessly fun! You just kinda hold down the shutter button and wave the camera around like your in-game sensitivity is on 10.0x, and then release and look at the cool little pattern you get!
This one was taken inside the Chihuly Glass Museum, specifically inside this one room where the entire ceiling was full of various coloured glass sculptures with warm light filtering through it.</description></item><item><title>Dreamweaver</title><link>/gallery/dreamweaver/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 16:21:32 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/dreamweaver/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Meteors</title><link>/gallery/meteors/</link><pubDate>Tue, 06 Jun 2023 16:12:26 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/meteors/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Faceless</title><link>/gallery/faceless/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 May 2023 19:28:36 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/faceless/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Hong Kong Alley</title><link>/gallery/hong-kong-alley/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 21:12:21 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/hong-kong-alley/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Taiwanese Alley</title><link>/gallery/taiwanese-alley/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 21:10:21 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/taiwanese-alley/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DSCF5603</title><link>/gallery/chinatown/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 20:40:05 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/chinatown/</guid><description>Usually you&amp;rsquo;re supposed to go back home with your family to celebrate Chinese New Year, much like Thanksgiving or Christmas. But I, being all alone in Tokyo, was unable to visit home, so I decided to just visit Yokohama Chinatown to see what was going on over there. Maybe I just got there too late or something, but there actually weren&amp;rsquo;t too many people. Some gift shops and restaurants were still open and all, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t seem all that lively.</description></item><item><title>Hot Dog Stand</title><link>/gallery/hot-dog-stand/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 19:24:50 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/hot-dog-stand/</guid><description>I was trying to get one of those really cool urban neon-Tokyo vibes shots of a man chilling at a food stall underneath neon lights. I think my composition kinda sucked though because I felt quite self-conscious about photographing strangers, which may or may not be a good thing. I&amp;rsquo;d like to make my photos have a more human and present feeling to them though.</description></item><item><title>It's Getting Dark</title><link>/gallery/its-getting-dark/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 17:00:54 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/its-getting-dark/</guid><description>Story time! Japan celebrates a statutory holiday called &amp;ldquo;Sports Day&amp;rdquo; every year. It&amp;rsquo;s a day dedicated to the pursuit of health and longevity through physical activities and general healthy lifestyle choices.
To celebrate this day, I joined a few of my fellow co-op student friends on a day trip to hike Mount Takao, or &amp;ldquo;Takaosan,&amp;rdquo; as the Japanese name would be romanized. Mount Takao is relatively accessible from central Tokyo, with a single train line travelling from Shinjuku Station all the way to the foot of Mount Takao.</description></item><item><title>Fleeting Respite</title><link>/gallery/fleeting-respite/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 21:02:02 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/fleeting-respite/</guid><description>Shibuya Yokochou is a magical and noisy street filled with small restaurants along one side of the entire street. It&amp;rsquo;s got that super down-to-earth cheap wooden tables and plastic chairs vibe all about, where people can yap about their lives and stuff while chowing down chicken skewers and beer. The entire street glows with a comfy amber aura throughout the evening while customers come and go.
The first time I came here, I vowed to never eat at any of the restaurants until my girlfriend would eventually come visit in Japan 7 months later.</description></item><item><title>DSCF4271</title><link>/gallery/shibuya-signs/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 19:48:03 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/shibuya-signs/</guid><description>Everyone with a camera has to take one those token Shibuya-Neon-Lights-City-That-Never-Sleeps type photographs when they visit Japan right? Well, here&amp;rsquo;s one!
This was taken on my first night ever checking out Shibuya. Despite already having seen tons of these types of photos online before moving to Tokyo, it still doesn&amp;rsquo;t compare to actually standing right in the middle of the visual and audial cacophany in-person. Seeing all the lights and signs which I couldn&amp;rsquo;t understand felt magical.</description></item><item><title>Silver Dragon</title><link>/gallery/silver-dragon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2021 21:33:28 -0600</pubDate><guid>/gallery/silver-dragon/</guid><description>Curious how it&amp;rsquo;s called the SILVER DRAGON yet the sign looks awfully golden&amp;hellip;</description></item></channel></rss>