<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>lights on Yifei Xu</title><link>yfxu.net/tags/lights/</link><description>Recent content in lights on Yifei Xu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-ca</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 15:09:46 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="yfxu.net/tags/lights/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DSCF9948</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/kitchen-sink/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 15:09:46 -0700</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/kitchen-sink/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DSCF5603</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/chinatown/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 20:40:05 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/chinatown/</guid><description>Usually you&amp;rsquo;re supposed to go back home with your family to celebrate Chinese New Year, much like Thanksgiving or Christmas. But I, being all alone in Tokyo, was unable to visit home, so I decided to just visit Yokohama Chinatown to see what was going on over there. Maybe I just got there too late or something, but there actually weren&amp;rsquo;t too many people. Some gift shops and restaurants were still open and all, but it didn&amp;rsquo;t seem all that lively.</description></item><item><title>Hot Dog Stand</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/hot-dog-stand/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 06:46:50 +0000</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/hot-dog-stand/</guid><description>I was trying to get one of those really cool urban neon-Tokyo vibes shots of a man chilling at a food stall underneath neon lights. I think my composition kinda sucked though because I felt quite self-conscious about photographing strangers, which may or may not be a good thing. I&amp;rsquo;d like to make my photos have a more human and present feeling to them though.</description></item><item><title>It's Getting Dark</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/its-getting-dark/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 17:00:54 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/its-getting-dark/</guid><description>Story time! Japan celebrates a statutory holiday called &amp;ldquo;Sports Day&amp;rdquo; every year. It&amp;rsquo;s a day dedicated to the pursuit of health and longevity through physical activities and general healthy lifestyle choices.
To celebrate this day, I joined a few of my fellow co-op student friends on a day trip to hike Mount Takao, or &amp;ldquo;Takaosan,&amp;rdquo; as the Japanese name would be romanized. Mount Takao is relatively accessible from central Tokyo, with a single train line travelling from Shinjuku Station all the way to the foot of Mount Takao.</description></item><item><title>Fleeting Respite</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/fleeting-respite/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 21:02:02 +0900</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/fleeting-respite/</guid><description>Shibuya Yokochou is a magical and noisy street filled with small restaurants along one side of the entire street. It&amp;rsquo;s got that super down-to-earth cheap wooden tables and plastic chairs vibe all about, where people can yap about their lives and stuff while chowing down chicken skewers and beer. The entire street glows with a comfy amber aura throughout the evening while customers come and go.
The first time I came here, I vowed to never eat at any of the restaurants until my girlfriend would eventually come visit in Japan 7 months later.</description></item><item><title>Silver Dragon</title><link>yfxu.net/gallery/silver-dragon/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 May 2021 21:33:28 -0600</pubDate><guid>yfxu.net/gallery/silver-dragon/</guid><description>Curious how it&amp;rsquo;s called the SILVER DRAGON yet the sign looks awfully golden&amp;hellip;</description></item></channel></rss>