<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>trees on Yifei Xu</title><link>/tags/trees/</link><description>Recent content in trees on Yifei Xu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-ca</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:55:43 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/trees/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Oddball</title><link>/gallery/oddball/</link><pubDate>Sat, 11 May 2024 00:55:43 -0600</pubDate><guid>/gallery/oddball/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DSCF9948</title><link>/gallery/kitchen-sink/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 15:09:46 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/kitchen-sink/</guid><description>In case you&amp;rsquo;re wondering what&amp;rsquo;s attached to the faucet, those are the pipes connected to a detachable dishwasher unit!
The house didn&amp;rsquo;t come with a dishwasher when it was built, so I guess some previous tenants bought a separate one. It was kind of annoying using it though, because you&amp;rsquo;re just not able to have a good user experience using the sink while it&amp;rsquo;s connected to the dishwasher.
There&amp;rsquo;s a little red button on the valve connected to the faucet that when pressed, will let the sink water flow out through the bottom.</description></item><item><title>DSCF9400</title><link>/gallery/santa-barbara-palm-trees/</link><pubDate>Sun, 27 Aug 2023 17:32:56 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/santa-barbara-palm-trees/</guid><description>Honestly this is kinda just a filler photo to put in the gallery to make myself seem more well-travelled ! aHA !
This photo was taken on a short trip with my girlfriend when we visited her Dad in Los Angeles. We spent 2 days in Santa Barbara, and it was the first time in many years that I&amp;rsquo;d been to a token California beach.
It was hot and humid, and neither my girlfriend nor I were able to think with more than six combined brain cells because we were both physically and mentally melting in real life!</description></item><item><title>Slow Down</title><link>/gallery/slow-down/</link><pubDate>Wed, 28 Jun 2023 19:46:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/slow-down/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DSCF6961</title><link>/gallery/red-umbrella/</link><pubDate>Thu, 11 May 2023 15:41:21 -0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/red-umbrella/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DSCF6123</title><link>/gallery/mt-fuji-from-owakudani/</link><pubDate>Thu, 04 May 2023 16:37:24 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/mt-fuji-from-owakudani/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DSCF5839</title><link>/gallery/naka-meguro-overblown/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Apr 2023 12:23:23 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/naka-meguro-overblown/</guid><description>This place gets reaaaaaal busy during Hanami, and understandably so. I came here on multiple different occasions just to take pictures of the cherry blossoms because yeah I&amp;rsquo;m basic like that.
But don&amp;rsquo;t worry, I made sure to get lots of random things in this picture to make it unique, and I also tuned up the saturation way past what they actually look like in real life. Rest assured, Naka-Meguro is still a very pretty place in person even if your eyeballs don&amp;rsquo;t have the latest saturation-boosting mods installed.</description></item><item><title>DSCF5755</title><link>/gallery/sakurain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 20:07:11 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/sakurain/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Lanterns</title><link>/gallery/lanterns/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 13:23:06 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/lanterns/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DSCF5446</title><link>/gallery/shrine-entrance/</link><pubDate>Sat, 03 Dec 2022 13:22:11 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/shrine-entrance/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DSCF4450</title><link>/gallery/mysterious-stairs/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 15:14:04 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/mysterious-stairs/</guid><description>Here&amp;rsquo;s some cool mysterious stairs we saw from when I hiked Mount Takao with some friends. There were an awful lot of stairs on this mountain hike. I don&amp;rsquo;t know if it made things easier or worse to be honest.</description></item><item><title>DSCF4447</title><link>/gallery/eerie-path/</link><pubDate>Mon, 10 Oct 2022 15:10:25 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/eerie-path/</guid><description>This was another shot I took during my ascent of Takaosan with some co-op friends in Japan. The thick fog is really cool for producing strange, eerie photos.</description></item><item><title>20210828_193529</title><link>/gallery/red-building/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 19:35:28 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/red-building/</guid><description>I took this photo while waiting in line for some apparently CRAZY GOOD ramen at Ramen Danbo! The line did not lie, the ramen was worth lining up for. I got some spicy ramen that my stomach didn&amp;rsquo;t end up quite agreeing with, but it was still an enjoyable experience! I think?</description></item><item><title>Suburban Cabana</title><link>/gallery/suburban-cabana/</link><pubDate>Sun, 02 May 2021 01:18:41 -0600</pubDate><guid>/gallery/suburban-cabana/</guid><description>I was just going for some generic infrastructure shots in this little community courtyard/garden area in Calgary, and I got this shot that looked a lot more like a travel advertisement for some nice California beaches or something. Pretty neat considering this was in Calgary!</description></item><item><title>20201030_110204</title><link>/gallery/offline/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 11:02:04 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/offline/</guid><description>The lighting in my bedroom was simply too impeccable at the time to pass up on quick photo. I love the moodiness in this photo, combined with the black electric fan that almost looks like it&amp;rsquo;s feeling sad, head tilted downwards, staring at the floor, standing out of the sunlight.</description></item></channel></rss>