<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>kagurazaka on Yifei Xu</title><link>/tags/kagurazaka/</link><description>Recent content in kagurazaka on Yifei Xu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-ca</language><lastBuildDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 01:15:40 +0900</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/kagurazaka/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Playground</title><link>/gallery/playground/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 01:15:40 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/playground/</guid><description>Part 3 of 3 Part 2
Uhhhhh I don&amp;rsquo;t actually know what to talk about here. I found this playground that looked somewhat creepy in the dead of the night. Maybe I&amp;rsquo;ll flesh out this part some other time XDDD</description></item><item><title>Ominous Alley</title><link>/gallery/ominous-alley/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:32:07 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/ominous-alley/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Street in Kagurazaka</title><link>/gallery/street-in-kagurazaka/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 May 2023 00:31:26 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/street-in-kagurazaka/</guid><description>Part 2 of 3 Part 1
The streets were so utterly silent and empty. I guess having gotten used to living in Ginza, being in a relatively more suburban community felt so off-putting because there were next to no sounds at all. And you&amp;rsquo;d think that in a metropolitan region as dense as Tokyo, SURELY there&amp;rsquo;d always be something happening somewhere right? Well I guess my brain is probably just deep fried from too much pop culture or media or whatever.</description></item><item><title>Nice Comfy Hotel</title><link>/gallery/nice-comfy-hotel/</link><pubDate>Sun, 30 Apr 2023 00:21:25 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/nice-comfy-hotel/</guid><description>Part 1 of 3 Jasmine and her friends arrived in Japan 1 day after I had to move out of my Ginza apartment. This left me with one day in-between to find some temporary accommodation. I elected to try staying in one of those msytical CAPSULE HOTELS that I&amp;rsquo;ve heard so much about on social media.
In case you haven&amp;rsquo;t seen photos of them, a capsule hotel is essentially just an accommodation where instead of renting out rooms or suites for the night, you rent out a small rectangular prism of space inside a wall that has nothing more than a twin-sized futon and probably a few hooks for your coats.</description></item></channel></rss>