<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>home on yfxu</title><link>/posts/</link><description>Recent content in home on yfxu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 11:51:00 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>About Me</title><link>/posts/about-me/</link><pubDate>Thu, 21 Dec 2000 15:44:25 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/about-me/</guid><description>Hi! I&amp;rsquo;m Yifei.
I&amp;rsquo;m a second-year computer engineering student at the University of Waterloo. At the moment, I&amp;rsquo;m trying to experience as wide a variety of software-related experiences as I can. I&amp;rsquo;m learning more about the world of technology every week, and I want to learn as much as I can.
I love playing rhythm games, arts and graphic design, and learning about anything that seems cool.</description></item><item><title>Four Years of osu! Mapping</title><link>/posts/four-years-of-osu-mapping/</link><pubDate>Wed, 27 Jan 2021 11:51:00 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/four-years-of-osu-mapping/</guid><description>The Start 2017-01-28 ‣ An - 花柳采 (Karyuusai) About 4 years ago, I published Karyuusai as my first serious attempt at making an osu! beatmap—meaning it was a pretty bad map. It had no structure, poor rhythm choices, and fairly garbage-tier aesthetics. But I kept mapping anyway, and I like to think that I got a little better making beatmaps since. Since I&amp;rsquo;ve spent so much time on this game, I figured I&amp;rsquo;d document my journey and some of the things I learned over these past 4 years as a tribute of sorts to that beatmap.</description></item><item><title>An Adventure in Building osulist</title><link>/posts/an-adventure-in-building-osulist/</link><pubDate>Sun, 24 Jan 2021 14:23:50 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/an-adventure-in-building-osulist/</guid><description>https://osulist.tk/
One of my favorite computer games is osu! (exclamation mark included) It&amp;rsquo;s a free rhythm game where the player&amp;rsquo;s goal is to click a bunch of circles that appear on the screen to the beat of a song. Songs are referred to as &amp;ldquo;beatmaps,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;maps&amp;rdquo; for short.
Over time, something I&amp;rsquo;ve noticed is that there isn&amp;rsquo;t a really great way to share multiple beatmaps with your friends. Say you&amp;rsquo;ve found a few beatmaps that you really like, and you want your friend to try playing them.</description></item><item><title>Getting Back Into Blogging</title><link>/posts/getting-back-into-blogging/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 20:48:20 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/getting-back-into-blogging/</guid><description>Back in early 2016, I created a Tumblr account because God knows why. Aha, actually it&amp;rsquo;s because I sorta wanted to exercise my writing skills somewhere outside of school, and blogging seemed like a cool way to achieve that. Part of me actually enjoyed writing because it was a nice way to sort out some thoughts in my head, and overall, it was just a peaceful experience.
At the time, I thought my posts were pretty cool.</description></item><item><title>Thoughts on Design</title><link>/posts/thoughts-on-design/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Nov 2020 20:48:20 -0700</pubDate><guid>/posts/thoughts-on-design/</guid><description>Many of my friends are well-invested into various forms of arts, either as hobbyists or professionals. So I hear a lot about the zeitgeist™ of whatever art communities are relevant at the time. As a result, I also start thinking more about art and its value (but usually it&amp;rsquo;s nothing more significant than &amp;ldquo;wohaoh this art looks very cool&amp;rdquo;).
Someone I know, being a part-time UI designer, spread their interest in graphic design over to me.</description></item></channel></rss>