<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>vancouver on Yifei Xu</title><link>/tags/vancouver/</link><description>Recent content in vancouver on Yifei Xu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-ca</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 15:09:46 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/vancouver/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DSCF9948</title><link>/gallery/kitchen-sink/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 15:09:46 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/kitchen-sink/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DSCF8801</title><link>/gallery/corner-store/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 15:18:08 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/corner-store/</guid><description>For 2 months during the summer this photo was taken, I worked full-time at a grocery store! It was a goal of mine for quite a while to experience working a job that isn&amp;rsquo;t just software engineering, where I sit in the same desk in front of the same computer screen and talk to the same people every day1, and so when I finally had an off-term from school, I was super stoked to try new things.</description></item><item><title>GULF OF GEORGIA CANNERY</title><link>/gallery/gulf-of-georgia-cannery/</link><pubDate>Fri, 19 Aug 2022 18:22:51 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/gulf-of-georgia-cannery/</guid><description>Just a shot of a building I saw at the Steveston Fisherman&amp;rsquo;s Wharf. I liked the lens flare that I accidentally got in the photo. It gives the photo a bit of a nostalgic feeling.</description></item><item><title>20220417_162453</title><link>/gallery/large-green-bridge/</link><pubDate>Sun, 17 Apr 2022 16:24:53 -0800</pubDate><guid>/gallery/large-green-bridge/</guid><description>The bridge was very green and the sky was very blue so I was like &amp;ldquo;mmm yes cool shot&amp;rdquo; and then I took the photo.</description></item><item><title>20210922_224502</title><link>/gallery/audio-visual-room/</link><pubDate>Wed, 22 Sep 2021 22:45:01 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/audio-visual-room/</guid><description>Isn&amp;rsquo;t this wall just so yellow??
I found this wall while roaming around the Life Building on UBC campus with Jasmine during some late night study trip. Or at least I think we were studying. Surely I was studying like a good student right? :D</description></item><item><title>20210828_193529</title><link>/gallery/red-building/</link><pubDate>Sat, 28 Aug 2021 19:35:28 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/red-building/</guid><description>I took this photo while waiting in line for some apparently CRAZY GOOD ramen at Ramen Danbo! The line did not lie, the ramen was worth lining up for. I got some spicy ramen that my stomach didn&amp;rsquo;t end up quite agreeing with, but it was still an enjoyable experience! I think?</description></item><item><title>20201030_110204</title><link>/gallery/offline/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 11:02:04 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/offline/</guid><description>The lighting in my bedroom was simply too impeccable at the time to pass up on quick photo. I love the moodiness in this photo, combined with the black electric fan that almost looks like it&amp;rsquo;s feeling sad, head tilted downwards, staring at the floor, standing out of the sunlight.</description></item></channel></rss>