<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>warm on Yifei Xu</title><link>/tags/warm/</link><description>Recent content in warm on Yifei Xu</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-ca</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 23:44:35 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/tags/warm/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>DSCF1111</title><link>/gallery/fire-sign/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 23:44:35 -0500</pubDate><guid>/gallery/fire-sign/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Hypnosis</title><link>/gallery/hypnosis/</link><pubDate>Wed, 06 Mar 2024 23:42:35 -0500</pubDate><guid>/gallery/hypnosis/</guid><description/></item><item><title>DSCF5755</title><link>/gallery/sakurain/</link><pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 20:07:11 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/sakurain/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Hong Kong Alley</title><link>/gallery/hong-kong-alley/</link><pubDate>Sat, 21 Jan 2023 21:12:21 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/hong-kong-alley/</guid><description/></item><item><title>Hot Dog Stand</title><link>/gallery/hot-dog-stand/</link><pubDate>Wed, 09 Nov 2022 19:24:50 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/hot-dog-stand/</guid><description>I was trying to get one of those really cool urban neon-Tokyo vibes shots of a man chilling at a food stall underneath neon lights. I think my composition kinda sucked though because I felt quite self-conscious about photographing strangers, which may or may not be a good thing. I&amp;rsquo;d like to make my photos have a more human and present feeling to them though.</description></item><item><title>Fleeting Respite</title><link>/gallery/fleeting-respite/</link><pubDate>Sat, 08 Oct 2022 21:02:02 +0900</pubDate><guid>/gallery/fleeting-respite/</guid><description>Shibuya Yokochou is a magical and noisy street filled with small restaurants along one side of the entire street. It&amp;rsquo;s got that super down-to-earth cheap wooden tables and plastic chairs vibe all about, where people can yap about their lives and stuff while chowing down chicken skewers and beer. The entire street glows with a comfy amber aura throughout the evening while customers come and go.
The first time I came here, I vowed to never eat at any of the restaurants until my girlfriend would eventually come visit in Japan 7 months later.</description></item><item><title>20201030_110204</title><link>/gallery/offline/</link><pubDate>Fri, 30 Oct 2020 11:02:04 -0700</pubDate><guid>/gallery/offline/</guid><description>The lighting in my bedroom was simply too impeccable at the time to pass up on quick photo. I love the moodiness in this photo, combined with the black electric fan that almost looks like it&amp;rsquo;s feeling sad, head tilted downwards, staring at the floor, standing out of the sunlight.</description></item></channel></rss>